(Penny:)Right.
(Amy:)So where are we going?
(Sheldon:)No, I meant turn right,
and you missed it.
(Sheldon:)Maybe you do need to know.
(indistinct chatter)
(Leonard:)What are we gonna tell
the girls?
(Howard:)It's not a problem.
(Leonard:)I mean without lying.
(Howard:)And now you've made it
a problem.
(Leonard:)Come on. We're
a couple of smart guys.
(Leonard:)I'm sure we can come up
with a way to explain this
(Leonard:)that doesn't make us
look bad.
(phone chimes)
Oh!
(Penny(at Howard's workshop, reading text):)The boys had to drive
all the way to San Bernardino
(Penny(at Howard's workshop, reading text):)for the solder and got a flat.
(phone chimes)
(Leonard:)They bought it.
(Howard:)But we're gonna have to
(Howard:)put the spare on
before we go back.
(Leonard:)Oh, you're good at this.
(Howard:)Well, I lie a lot.
MAN:
Hey, guys, thank you
(Man:)for being a part of our
test screening. You're about
(Man:)to be one of the first audiences
to see Suicide Squad.
(applause and cheering)
Hey!
(laughs)
You were right.
Oh, I keep telling you...
(Howard:)good things happen
to bad people.